杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 这正是我们想要的。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: This
is doing what we want.
我们已经为我们的网站设计了一个基本的结构。
So we've got kind of a basic structure for
our site.
我们得到了一些点击之间。
We've got some clicks between.
但是我希望这个按钮更加明显一点。
But I want this button to be
a little more noticeable.
所以我要在主题 UI 中使用一个变体来设置一个按钮样式,
So I'm gonna use a variant in
Theme UI to set up a button style,
因为我想进入那个系统。
because I wanna be able to access that.
因此，要做到这一点，我可以跳转到我们的主题 UI。
So to do that,
I can jump into our Theme UI.
我要定义一个按钮，我想要这是一个中空的按钮。
And I'm just gonna define a button and
I want this to be a hollow button.
我们不想引起太多的注意。
We don't wanna draw a ton
of attention to it.
它不是一个行动的号召，它只是一件你可以做的事情。
It's not like a call to action,
it's just a thing you can do.
我要设置背景颜色为背景。
And I'm gonna set the background
color to background.
注意，这只是一个普通的样式对象。
And note,
this is just a regular style object.
就像你用 SX 道具一样,
The same way that you would do it
if you were using the SX prop,
你也要在这里做。
you're gonna do it here as well.
所以我们要做背景调查。
So we're gonna do
the background of background.
我要设置的边界，将主题，我们会设置它像2像素的固体。
I'm gonna setup the border, will be theme,
and we'll set it to be like 2 px solid.
让我们添加 theme.colors.primary。
And let's add theme.colors.primary.
然后我可以将 borderRadius 设置为10。
Then I can set the borderRadius to 10.
让我们将文本的颜色设置为主色。
Let's set the color of
the text to primary color.
我还要将显示设置为 inline-block。
I'm also gonna set
the display to inline-block.
让我们将 fontFamily 设置为 heading，将 fontWeight 设置为 bold。
Let's set the fontFamily to heading,
the fontWeight to bold.
我会把这个做成一个很漂亮的按钮，给它加点衬垫。
I'll make this a really fancy button,
give it some padding.
我们将把文字修饰去掉。
We'll take the textDecoration out.
确保它没有被划线,
Make sure that it doesn't get underlined,
我们已经用纽扣的轮廓来引起注意了。
we're already calling attention
to it with the button outline.
然后我们甚至要给这些 CSS 转换。
And then we're gonna even give
this some CSS transitions.
我把它设置为200毫秒,
So I'm gonna set it up
to run 200 milliseconds,
这是个很好的过渡长度。
that's a good transition length.
我们使用线性因为我们要做颜色转换
We use linear because we're
gonna do color transitions, and
以我的经验来看，应该是干净的。
in my experience that tends to be clean.
这是一个线性宽松。
This one it's done with a linear easing.
最后，我们要设置一些聚焦样式，因为,
And then finally, we wanna set up
some focus styles because again,
我们希望能成功。
we want that to work.
我之前没有表现出来。
And I didn't show that earlier.
这就是我所说的。
So this is kinda what I'm talking about.
你可以看到这个是有风格的,
And you can see this one is styled,
在我的标签上有一个提纲。
there's an outline that
shows up on my tab to it.
而且很漂亮也很干净。
And it's nice and clean.
它使用相同的颜色。
It uses the same color.
它与文本的偏移量。
It's offset from the text.
但是如果我默认选项卡下降到这个链接，它被突出显示，它很容易看到。
But if I tab down to this link by default,
it's highlighted, it's easy to see.
所以违约并不是一件坏事。
And so defaults aren't a bad thing.
您可以保留默认值。
You can leave the defaults in place.
但是如果你真的想让它看起来有点时尚
But if you really wanna make
it look kinda styled, and
如果你想控制外观，千万不要移除焦点样式。
you wanna take control over the look,
never remove focus styles.
永远，永远，永远不要移除焦点样式，除非你要替换它们。
Never, never, never remove focus
styles unless you're replacing them.
所以我们要做的就是让这些更加定制化。
So what we're doing is we're just
gonna make these more custom.
所以我的焦点风格这里将是一个背景颜色突出。
So my focus style here is going to
be a background color highlight.
我要使用一个轮廓，我们将它设置为2px 的固体。
I'm gonna use an outline and
we'll set that up to be 2px solid.
主题颜色.primary。
The theme colors.primary.
好的，然后我们把 outlineOffset 设置为2。
All right, and
then we'll set that outlineOffset to 2.
然后我们也想要一些悬停样式，如果你悬停在它上面。
And then we also want some hover
styles if you hover over it.
因此，让我们添加一个悬停风格。
So let's add a hover style.
如果你把鼠标悬停在这个上面，我们就把背景做成高光。
And we'll just make the background
highlight, if you hover over this.
好的，我已经做了这个。
Okay, so I've done this.
但是我们还没有真正使用它。
But we're not actually using it yet.
所以方差的工作方式是，任何在顶层的，不是保留的
So the way that variance work is anything
that's at top level that's not a reserved
就像颜色和字体一样，我们可以定义一个主题。
word, so like the colors or the fonts,
we can just define a theme.
所以如果你想你可以命名这个到你的主题，你可以
And so if you wanted to you could
namespace this to your theme and you could
比如说，主题文档点击主键或者其他什么，如果你想让它工作的话。
say, theme docs dot button dot primary or
something if you wanted to make that work.
在大多数网站上，我发现复杂度并没有那么高
In most sites, I've found that
the complexity doesn't get that high so
你可以用一些合理的名字，不一定是很重的名字。
you can get away with just sensible names,
not necessarily heavily named space names.
根据团队规模的不同，你的成绩可能会有所不同
Your mileage may vary depending
on the size of your team and
有多少不同的人会碰它。
how many different people
are gonna touch it.
为了实际使用这个，我们可以回到这个索引
So to actually use this we can
go back out to this index and
我希望能够设置这一个有一个变体。
I want to be able to set
this one to have a variant.
所以我要把 thesx prop 设置为 variant。
So I'm gonna set thesx prop to variant.
然后我们用点表示法。
And then we just use dot notation.
所以按我说的做，空心的，好吗？
So button.hollow, okay?
但是为了实现这个功能，我们需要切换到 JSX pragma。
But in order for this to work,
we need to switch over to the JSX pragma.
所以让我把 react 放在这里
So let me replace react up here with
来自 theme-ui 的 JSX pragma，好吗？
the JSX pragma from the theme-ui, okay?
所以我们得到了 JSX pragma，这意味着我们可以访问 sx 道具。
So we've got the JSX pragma and that
means that we have access to the sx prop.
我们所做的一切都表明，这是一个空心按钮，基于我们的方差。
And all we've done is signify that this is
a hollow button, based on our variance.
假设我没有打错任何字母，我们就有了一个按钮
And assuming I didn't typo anything,
there we go, we've got a button and
它可以选择所有的风格。
it picks up all the styles.
所以当我开始点击你可以看到它现在仍然显示一个轮廓,
So when I start clicking around you
can see it now still shows an outline,
但是这个轮廓看起来更像是品牌。
but that outline looks
a little more on brand.
所以我们希望这是非常明显的。
So we want this to be very obvious.
当你进入一个按钮的轮廓应该是
When you get into a button
the outline should be
非常明显，因为在一个繁忙的页面，当有人通过点击他们
very noticeable because on a busy page
when somebody is tapping through they
应该知道他们的键盘当前突出显示的是什么。
should know exactly what is currently
highlighted with their keyboard.
所以这并不像我认为你不会提交设计师的作品，但是
So this isn't like I don't think you
would submit that for designer works, but
这对于那些通过键盘浏览你网站的人来说是显而易见的,
this can be really apparent to whoever
is keyboard tabbing through your site,
这是当前被选中的按钮。
that that is the button
that is currently selected.
所以从那里开始，我认为我们可以保存我们的工作。
So from there,
I think we can save our work.
然后我们将继续进一步定制这个。
And then we'll move on to
further customizing this.
演讲者2: 变体按钮是什么？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What was that
the button of variant?
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 是的，在主题用户界面中的变体,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Yeah,
so variant in Theme UI,
只是一种给样式命名的方式，这使得它们可以被重用
are just a way to give a name set of
styles, which makes them reuseable
而不需要一个物体，你掉进 sx 道具或什么东西。
without having to have an object that
you drop into the sx prop or something.
所以，是的，我们已经设置了主题 UI 和 gatsby 配置
So yeah, we have set up the Theme UI and
gatsby config and
安装这些依赖项。
install these dependencies.
我写了一个布局文件，设置了一个自定义主题
I wrote a layout file,
setup a custom theme and
然后重写索引和历史页面来使用这种布局。
then rewrote the index and
history pages to use that layout.
所以，让我们承诺这一点。
So let's commit that.
添加主题 UI，把它向上推。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Add Theme UI,
push it up.